(Penny:)Oh, my God, I love this chicken.
(Sheldon:)Oh, you know what they say,
"The best things in life are free."
(Penny:)You're right. I eat your food a lot.
How about this?
(Penny:)You can raid my fridge
any time you want.
(Sheldon:)Oh, that's very kind of you.
(Sheldon:)Next time I have a hankering
to wash down a D-cell battery...
(Sheldon:)...with a jar of old pickle juice,
I'll come a-knocking.
(Howard:)Hey, Raj, you didn't send your RSVP in.
(Howard:)I'm supposed to ask you
if you're bringing someone.
(Raj:)I'll let you know.
Could you make it soon?
There's a battle over seating.
ln one corner, Bernadette's mom.
ln the other three, mine.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, I hate wedding receptions.
l wish the bride and groom...
(Sheldon:)...would take a cue from Bilbo Baggins.
(Sheldon:)Slip on the ring, disappear,
and everyone goes home.
Oh, you liked Professor Geyser's wedding.
They had a make-your-own-sundae bar.
(Sheldon:)Oh, that was a night to remember.
Do you know, on one trip,
l just had a bowl of nuts.
(Howard:)Anyway, you gotta let me know
if you have a plus-one.